Oh, right...
The full moon turns you minks into
those so-called Sulong berserkers.
Jack!
You've gone too far, you damn samurai!
That you even made it here... That's on us!
But you'll never get this close to Kaido again!
You-gara stay back!
Jack became our sworn enemy the moment
he ravaged our thousand-year-old dukedom.
We told him countless times
the samurai wasn't there...
I am that warrior they
claimed was not there, Jack!
It was you...!
I owe them my life!
I will repay them a hundred
times over in this battle!
Wait, Master...
Please save your strength for Kaido.
You too, Your Grace!
Very well, I leave them to you.
Thank you.
In that case, we'll use every bit of
our strength to take down Kaido!
Stand your ground!
Sulong doesn't last long!
Bring it on!
We're beasts, too!
They've started.
That blowhard Jack went up there with them?
Unlike you, he knows how to read the room.
Huh?!
King... You and I aren't gonna
have a problem here...
are we?!
Shinobu?!
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Arts!
Quietly...
Oh no!
Shinobu!
That was a pretty good plan.
However...
its execution was poor!
Shinobu!
Lord Momonosuke!
How shameful to have been
rendered unconscious!
Let us try again!
What the...?!
What?! He's floating!
Flying even!
Too high!
This is terrifying!
Lord Momonosuke!
What is causing this?!
On behalf of Kaido,
I'll see to your execution!
What's that?!
For real, what is that?
Sangoro!
Sanji?!
Sanji!
You rock!
Hand over the brat! He must be
erased from this world!
Lord Momonosuke!
Hey, Momo!
When you shouted out your name...
it gave me the chills!
Sangoro...!
Shinobu, look after Momo!
I shall!
Thank you, Sangoro!
The Kozuki must be extinguished!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No good...!
I'm in trouble...!
Cut it out, bird brain!
At this rate, I'll wind up dead
with a hole in my stomach!
Just a hole?! I intend to break you in half!
Where's your little vanishing act?!
It's only optical camouflage...
Just let go of me!
This is it!
Sanji!
That attack was crazy...
Yamabro! Take care of Momo!
Help Shinobu protect him!
What?! Are you sure?!
Of course I'm sure!
Right! That actually makes sense...
b-because he's my son!
Just go!
Yeah, leave it to me!
A father must look after his son!
Hey, don't ignore me!
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
Your father is on his way!
Wait! Tarry here, I say!
I won't let you get away!
All you louts!
Let's kill every last samurai raiding this place...
and start the banquet over!
As for you!
The wedding! The tea party!
Even this banquet...!
It takes a special kind of someone
to always ruin other people's fun!
I'll kill you in a way that
more than pays for your meddling!
You'll die a miserable death!
Hegemony!
Crap!
Are you trying to kill me?!
What is that hag, a monster?!
I heard she's a pirate captain from overseas
with as much infamy to her name as Kaido!
What?! Does that mean we're
basically facing two Kaidos?!
I wanna go help Momo and Sanji,
but she'll just follow me right to them!
Damn you, Straw Hat...!
I'm surprised you were able to dodge that!
Come, Zeus!
Zeus, what's the hold up?!
Why, you little...!
She saw us!
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's impossible!
Nami! She'll kill us!
Bad boy!
Come back here!
O-Okay, Mama...
Zeus!
Me or Big Mom!
Who do you choose?!
I can't disobey Mama!
Enough already!
Naaamiii!
You damn Cat Burglar!
This is all my fault...!
Sorry, Mama.
I promise not to wander off anymore,
so please forgive me!
Oh, so now you're back on my side?
How can I trust someone who would
follow an annoying tramp like her?!
What should I do?!
How can I earn back your trust?!
You know what to do.
I need you to kill that bitch.
The watch?
♪ Threw it away! ♪
♪ I'm the wind, baby! ♪
You already know, right, Zeus?!
If you hold back, you're history!
No!
Soul Sensor: Activate!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Rest in peace!
I hate you!
We are so through!
Someone help me!
Wings?
♪ I will spread them wide! ♪
♪ 'Cause I am a bird! ♪
– ♪ Flutter my wings and fly away! ♪
– ♪ High in the sky and on the wind! ♪
♪ I'm Free Rider Franky! ♪
There. You've been cut!
– What?!
Huh?
Oops! I think I ran over something!
Oh well!
As long as it wasn't a flower.
Big Bro!
Mama...!
Mama!
Now they've done it!
They're dead men!
He ran over Big Mom with his bike!
Big Bro!
Thank you, Franky!
Nami!
Are you okay?!
Oh, yeah! I'm fabulous!
With Big Bro here, we're all set!
Go! Samurai warriors!
Looks like it's started.
Well, well...
Look who they ran over.
Care to partake, Nico Robin?
Why, I'd be delighted.
Nice!
Franky and Brook came through as always!
In that case...
I'll help Kin'emon!
Here I go!
There you are!
You're okay!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Who are you?!
Hey, Shinobu!
He's our ally!
You can trust him!
What? Our ally?!
It's safer to be with him
than to be by yourselves.
See ya!
Are you truly an ally?
Yeah!
Very well.
I will trust you.
Please tell us your name!
– What?!
I am...
I am Kozuki Oden!
I shall protect you!
Father...
Lord Oden...
Fath... er?
Breasts...
Horns...!
You are not my father!
You are far too suspicious!
You are certainly our enemy!
What?!
Smoke Escape Technique!
Wait!
Why are you running away?!
We're heavily outnumbered.
This will take forever.
You're right!
Fighting these underlings is a waste of time!
The dinosaurs of the Soaring Six
that Denjiro mentioned...
Should we go take their heads?
We might be a little outclassed...
but we can at least stall them!
Really now, I didn't see that coming...
Big Mom's gonna go berserk!
Run for it!
You're popping up one after another...
Straw Hats!
Soul King. How nice to see you again.
I see your little group is made up
of some truly rare creatures!
You have good taste!
You like my iron body, you old hag?
My name is...
Franky!
A bona fide cyborg!
I'm not just rare, but strong, too!
Cut it out, guys!
We need to run! She's an Emperor!
An Emperor...?
We run from those?
Hey, Nami.
Don't you want...
to make our captain...
the King of the Pirates?!
Franky...
Radical...
Bea–
Wha...?!
What kind of giant monstrosities...?!
Hey!
You were assigned to a different banquet hall!
Numbers!
No!
They're as big as Oars!
What are they?!
It's like Thriller Bark all over again...!
Are these the guys Kaido
bought from Punk Hazard?!
The failed recreations of the ancient giants?!
How lovely...!
In that monster's hand...!
The Brachio Tank!
Wasn't Usopp's team in there?!
Hands off the hardware, you overgrown mole!
Franky...
Radical...
Beam!
My laser beam...
is unstoppable now!
Are you sure you didn't want
to shoot it this way...
Iron Man?
Your arm, if I may!
Fishman Jujutsu...
Mil Fleurs...
...Whirlpool Shoulder Throw!
...Delphinium!
Damn you, Jinbe!
I remember what you did to my fleet!
I'll kill you, too!
You're welcome to try!
How was that?
Even better than I expected!
She'll return angrier than ever!
You certainly are a remarkable woman!
My bad!
Thanks for the assist, you two!
I'm just glad you're unharmed!
Now then...
It's the moment you've all been waiting for.
Come in, Commander Chopper!
Usopp!
Wake up! Usopp!
We got a call from Franky!
Hey! You guys are okay, right?!
The Brachio Tank is the world's greatest...
Do you remember the promise?!
The pro... mise...?
A pirate made of iron...
the Iron Pirate!
It's docking time!
Dock...
...ing?
– Docking!
Oh, I can see the sky.
Okay, I think I can get up from here.
Don't move!
Your Awesomeness!
Shut up. I'm on break.
It's Straw Hat!
What?! Straw Hat?!
And he isn't alone?!
Hey, Zoro!
There you are, Luffy!
Where are you headed?
Up to where Kaido is!
I'll come with you.
As if I would just let you by!
What's that giant creature down there?!
Alright!
Gum-Gum...
Rocket!
I can make it!
Kaido's up there?
Yeah! Kin'emon's group is
already up there fighting!
Almost there!
Dammit!
You bastards are mine, now!
This is as far as you go!
We'll never get up there like this!
They've got the sky totally blocked off!
Here we go-go-go!
Let's do this thing!
– Docking Formation!
Black Rhino: Stand By!
– Brachio Head: Change!
Sorry! This robot is a single-seater.
What?!
You can't do this!
Those two are...
Usohachi! Chopperemon!
You doing okay?!
We can't thank you enough for your
sacrifice back at the pleasure hall!
Guys, there are more important
things at hand!
At hand!
Feast your eyes on the wonders of docking!
Feast your eyes!
Iron Pirate...
General Franky!
Here I go!
Franky Cannon!
Of course you shot it yourself!
Of course!
Super!
Jaki's down!
Hey, this is real bad!
Let's just get away from here!
Good thinking!
Where's Momo?
I guess he got away...
This suit is annoyingly sturdy...
Oh, I'm sorry!
This situation kind of tickles my funny bone.
We're still surrounded by enemies.
But for some reason,
I can't imagine losing.
You're right!
Yeah, me neither!
It's strange. Why do we feel this way?
It's obvious, isn't it?!
It's because Sir Straw Hat is with us!
I thought I could get there just by jumping.
Damn. Guess it won't be that easy.
I'll come with you.
Let's just get to the top!
What a pain...
Can all these bastards fly?
Tear off their wings,
and they're just caterpillars.
That's horrific! Your analogies
are always so scary!
So these are the Superstars
we've heard so much about.
They may look tough, but they
don't hold a candle to our captain!
Yeah!
It's my duty as a navigator to get
the captain to his destination!
Super count on me!
Let the General Franky clear the way for you!
Let's go, Captain!
Yeah! One more time! Ready?!
Everyone! I'll leave the rest to you!
Back us up!
I'm gonna go...
kick Kaido's ass!